<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cara Van Uden</title><link>https://caravanuden.com/</link><description>Recent content on Cara Van Uden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© {year}</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://caravanuden.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>tbd</title><link>https://caravanuden.com/blog/tbd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://caravanuden.com/blog/tbd/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Google text normalization challenge with LSTM encoder/decoder</title><link>https://caravanuden.com/projects/text-norm/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://caravanuden.com/projects/text-norm/</guid><description>tl;dr:
This project takes on text normalization with an LSTM encoder/decoder.
Github repo
Jupyter notebook for the data preprocessing, model training, and model prediction code.
If you want to load my encoder-decoder model, download the hdf5 file and run the following lines of code to play around with my trained model:
import load_model from keras.models
model = load_model(&amp;lsquo;saved_model.hdf5&amp;rsquo;)
If you want to see my predicted results on the 100,000 tokens in the test set, take a look at the &amp;ldquo;test_predictions&amp;rdquo; file.</description></item><item><title>Spotify playlist recommendation challenge with NeuMF</title><link>https://caravanuden.com/projects/spotify-recsys/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://caravanuden.com/projects/spotify-recsys/</guid><description>tl;dr:
This project takes on playlist recommendation with a neural recommendation system. Github repo Overview Spotify is an online music streaming service with over 140 million active users and over 30 million tracks. One of its popular features is the ability to create playlists, and the service currently hosts over 2 billion playlists.
This year&amp;rsquo;s challenge focuses on music recommendation, specifically the challenge of automatic playlist continuation. By suggesting appropriate songs to add to a playlist, a recommender system can increase user engagement by making playlist creation easier, as well as extending listening beyond the end of existing playlists.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://caravanuden.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://caravanuden.com/about/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a machine learning engineer at Wayfair, where I work on competitor product matching at the terabytes of data scale. My team won the Wayfair Hackathon in 2019 with our Clusterbrowse project.
I graduated from Dartmouth College, where I studied Computer Science and Cognitive Science. My thesis compared representations learned by various CNN architectures to those of the human ventral visual pathway.
Check out my resume.</description></item></channel></rss>